(All characters and organisations in this drama are fictional.)
(Filming with minors followed broadcast guidelines,)
(and generative AI was used in select scenes.)
(Geumje Police Station)
(Episode 5)
Running away again?
If you are going to run, do it right this time.
So we never have to see each other again.
Mom.
Sweetheart.
Mom, that must have been really hard.
Yes.
Gyeol kept saying he wanted to see you,
So I brought him along.
Did everything go okay?
Here, eat this.
Why did you buy this?
You need to eat.
That guy looks really familiar.
Who is he?
Where have I seen him?
I definitely know that face.
- Honey, let's go. - Honey?
Honey?
Sure, let's do that. Gyeol, let's go. Come on, honey.
Let's go.
That's her, right?
That was Gyu Rim, right? I was not seeing things, was I?
We searched everywhere...
And could not find a single trace of her,
And she just shows up here?
Why was she at a police station?
No, that's not even the point. She called that monkey-faced guy...
"honey." So that guy is her husband?
She went and got married already?
She must be out of her mind.
How could she dump you and end up with that monkey guy?
And who was that kid? Her son?
If he's her son, that doesn't make sense.
No way that's possible.
- Jung Woo. - What? Why?
Drive for me.
Sorry, that startled you, didn't it?
No, nothing to be sorry about.
But why did you do that all of a sudden?
- Well, it's because... - That man from earlier,
You didn't want him looking down on Mom, right?
Is that right?
If he thinks you're her husband, he wouldn't dare mess with her,
And you look dependable.
Dependable?
Is that true?
That doesn't mean you're husband material for my mom,
So don't get too excited.
- Gyeol, no games starting today. - What?
And you too.
No matter how much Gyeol begs or threatens you,
Don't bring him to a place like this.
This is no place for a kid.
Well, just make sure you never have to come here again.
So eat this tofu properly.
And never come back to a rough place like this.
Got it?
Am I really banned from games?
Yes, I should have banned them a long time ago.
You said if I studied just as hard, you would let me play.
- You're banned, end of story. - But who was that guy?
- That's not fair. - I definitely know that face.
You're banned, period.
- Mom. - I can't figure it out.
- Mom. - Han Gyeol, enough.
Wait up.
Pull over.
What?
I said pull over.
Hey!
Why did you only ask for 100,000 dollars?
If you were going to do it, ask for 100 million dollars.
Am I only worth 100,000 dollars to you?
What is he talking about?
You said you wouldn't run away.
That no matter what happened, you wouldn't run.
You promised.
I'm sorry.
Sorry?
You're sorry?
Do you know what my life was like after you disappeared?
For years, I searched for you, wandering all over the world,
Like a madman who'd lost his mind.
Do you have any idea what I went through?
But you...
You got married and had a child,
And you're just living your life like nothing ever happened?
- Mu Jin. - Shut up.
How could you play with someone's life like that?
Who do you think you are to mess with people's lives?
Did you ever even love me?
Are you even human? You heartless girl.
Don't.
Hey, man.
This guy's completely lost it.
Kim Mu Jin.
I'm going to take a walk before I head in.
You're not thinking of doing anything stupid, are you?
Like I always say,
There are plenty of other fish in the sea.
I'll be back before we open for dinner.
(Suragan Side Dishes)
That's it.
It's that guy.
It's him, right?
Nine years ago, at the restaurant, he said he liked you and was all...
Oh, right.
On second thought, that wasn't him.
Right, that guy and this guy look totally different.
I must have been mistaken.
Mister.
- What? - Why are you such a bad actor?
Who's a bad actor? Me? No, I'm not.
He looks similar, but it's not him, right?
Right.
I thought so for a second, but I guess he was mistaken too.
Why? Do I seem like a bad actor too?
A little?
Trust me. It wasn't him.
What are we going to do?
Oh my, what a lovely sight.
You really look like a family.
Let's go.
(Suragan Side Dishes)
Like this, as one big family,
Wouldn't it be nice if the three of you...
Lived together happily?
Such a lovely sight. Stay right there.
Smile. Now get closer. Wow, what a picture.
Why are you just standing there and taking this?
I've tried to be patient with this woman,
But this is too much.
Who are you trying to pair up with whom?
How could Han Gyu Rim and your family...
- ever be one family? - Gyu Young.
- Why did that vixen show up again? - I know.
It's wishful thinking. Can't I even have wishful thinking?
Mom, that's enough.
So you're saying your wish...
Is for Han Gyu Rim? Why her?
Go look somewhere else. Find a woman who's on your son's level...
Is that any way to talk to an adult?
Why did you hit me? Did I say something wrong?
I only said what was true. Gyeol, tell her.
She only said what was true.
The kind of true things that get you in trouble.
Hey, Han Gyeol.
My goodness, our Han Gyeol is a regular prosecutor.
- Good job. - Mom, that's enough.
What's with you?
You used to say your mom was too good...
For Kim Woo Bin even if he begged.
Have you already fallen for that rice thief?
What did you say? Did you just call my son...
A rice thief?
Why, you...
You 100-year-old vixen.
Mom, why are you being like this? Just stop.
Ma'am, did you just call me a vixen?
Did you see me acting like a vixen?
Well, did you? Did you see my son stealing rice?
- No, but... - Come here.
Hey, Han Gyeol. You'd better get your head on straight too.
You'll go from Han Gyeol to Jo Gyeol in an instant, you punk.
- Shut your mouth. Can't you? - Why are you doing this to me?
You'll become Jo Gyeol. Jo Gyeol.
Wow.
I wonder what fool would ever marry a brat like that.
If you ever bring home a girl like that,
I'll dig my own grave. So you'd better be smart.
Am I crazy enough to date a girl like that?
Salt. I should throw some salt. Bring me some salt.
Even salt is a waste. That's enough. Stop it.
Hey, I said let go. It hurts.
Hey, it hurts.
Gosh, that hurts.
You're just brutishly strong. Am I going to have a bruise?
Seriously, what's wrong with you?
- What? - You don't come to the shop.
Even if you heard what she was saying,
You would've just pretended not to and left.
So why are you picking a fight over everything today...
And causing a scene?
Because I hate the idea of becoming a family with that rice thief.
Heung Sik? What's wrong with him?
I've told you a million times. If you're going to date someone,
Date someone who's at least half a step above you.
You seem to be mistaken about something.
- I'm not that great of a person. - I'm so pathetic,
Lacking, and shabby...
Heung Sik is 1,000, 10,000 times better and more wonderful than me.
So you're saying you'll even marry that rice thief?
I'd be grateful if he'd have me.
Have you lost your mind?
I'm more sane than I've ever been.
Just because that rice thief...
Saved you when you collapsed on the street,
You seem to be all touched, but...
Didn't you save his mother when she collapsed?
So that makes you even, doesn't it?
If it weren't for his mom and Heung Sik,
I would have died back then.
So?
Are you really...
Going to try to make something happen with those people?
I'm dead set against it.
I'm not the one who's being asked to get married.
Why are you meddling in my life?
Since when have you ever cared so much about me?
I'm worried my own life will be ruined...
Because of you.
Please, I'm begging you.
When I introduce you as family to people,
Even if I can't be incredibly proud,
At least don't embarrass me. Okay?
You'd be better off seeing that guy you met eight years ago.
At least he was good-looking.
Why are you bringing him up all of a sudden?
You startled me. You were crazy about that guy.
- You talked in your sleep. - When did I ever do that?
Why are you yelling all of a sudden?
See? You do still like him.
You're definitely not over him, are you?
Stop talking such nonsense.
If you're going to keep clashing with the owner,
Don't come to the shop again.
I was just trying to give you some advice.
Did that leave a bruise?
(No Married Couples Allowed)
Are you trying to shut down the restaurant?
No couples, and no married couples.
- How are you going to do business? - People who want to come will come.
Is it your dream to go out of business?
Is something wrong?
No.
Aren't you busy?
What is it?
Do I need a reason to come here?
You said we should eat sometime.
Sorry, but let's do it another time. Okay?
Something is definitely wrong. What is it?
You should just go.
- Why? - Just because.
Go home, for today.
- Give it back. - Go home before causing trouble.
If this restaurant goes under,
I think I might actually kill you.
What is it?
Mu Jin saw Gyu Rim today.
Who is Gyu Rim?
The Han Gyu Rim from back in the day?
When? How? What happened?
It was an unbelievable coincidence.
Is it okay to just let him go like this?
Seo Hyun, what if Mu Jin is on his way and...
What if he crashes his car?
Did he say she's still pretty?
Is he still into her? Is he dying to be with her?
Does he want to get back together with her?
Gosh, I shouldn't have told you.
But you don't have to worry.
How can I not worry?
I saw what Han Gyu Rim did to Mu Jin.
I saw how broken he was.
I know how much he's still in love with her.
She's married, Gyu Rim.
She even has a son.
- She has a son? - He didn't know it was her son,
And there was a problem while they were playing a game...
Unbelievable.
He ended up meeting her because of the son.
Her son is that old? How old is he?
I think he said he was eight.
Han Gyu Rim and Mu Jin broke up eight years ago.
Was Han Gyu Rim cheating on him?
You don't like this place either?
Did they get a new chef here? Why does it taste like this?
It's delicious.
I think it's still delicious.
If you think it's so good, you can have it all.
Get it out of here. I can't even stand the smell.
You hate everything I bring you.
Why have you completely lost your appetite all of a sudden?
I guess it means I'm about to die.
After hearing that Chairman Kim has a grandchild,
You're not just being jealous, are you?
His son is younger than Mu Jin,
But he's already married with a child...
Who is Mu Jin?
Why are you talking about someone I don't even know?
(Mu Jin)
- Okay. I'll call you back. - You really didn't do anything?
Do what out of nowhere?
I'm asking if you and Mom really didn't do anything...
To Gyu Rim.
What are you talking about? This is completely random.
That's not who Gyu Rim is. Even if the world were ending,
She's not the kind of person who could do that.
Either you or Mom must have done something.
What did you do?
What on earth did you do to Gyu Rim?
You call me out of the blue,
And I don't know why you're being like this,
But I told you clearly eight years ago.
Mom and I didn't do anything. Han Gyu Rim came to see us herself.
She said she would break up with you for 100,000 dollars.
You heard it with your own ears.
Are you still hung up on Han Gyu Rim?
It's been so long since you two broke up.
Just how long are you going to keep this up?
(Chairman Hong Ok Seon)
It's Mu Jin.
I didn't ask.
Can't you be the one to reach out to Mu Jin first?
He broke up with Han Gyu Rim a long time ago.
(Chairman Hong Ok Seon)
Han Gyu Rim was a good person.
You and I were too harsh.
Why are you talking so much? I can't get any work done.
This is a place of business.
Can't you separate business from your personal life?
Is that it?
Is it really that bad?
The doctor...
He told me to prepare for the worst.
That's impossible.
- I'm healthy without a single ache. - Did you get it?
But why you?
Excuse me.
Yes.
I'm sorry, honey.
For showing you such a weak side of me.
I really tried to hide it from you.
Don't say things like that.
If you keep talking like that, I'm going to get really upset.
If it's just one,
Will that be enough?
I heard targeted therapy is expensive.
No.
I'll figure it out.
Even if I die right now, I've loved you with no regrets.
So that's enough for me.
No. I'll save you.
No matter what, I'm going to save you.
So don't you worry about money. All right?
Honey!
What do I do, Hee Na?
My mom's having an affair.
Hey, how is that an affair? Your father passed away, right?
Your mother can date if she wants.
I'm telling you, this isn't just a normal relationship.
Of all people, she had to meet a bastard like him.
What kind of bastard? A bird? You mean, like a bird?
You can tell right away, can't you?
He's obviously our age or even younger.
Why would he be dating my mom?
- It's obvious. - Totally.
- A gigolo. - A gigolo.
- Darn it. Exactly. - Darn it, what do we do?
What am I going to do now?
I think she already gave that bastard...
Hundreds of thousands of dollars.
What? Hundreds of thousands?
The worst part is, there's no telling...
How much more he'll bleed her for.
Hey, have you talked to your mom about this?
No.
If I let on that I know, she'll cut me off.
I won't get my inheritance.
My younger brother knows all about it too,
But he's not saying a word because he wants his inheritance too.
Oh, wait a minute. You...
Have you tried looking this "bird" guy up?
Just his number.
I swiped it while my mom was in the shower.
Hey, give it to me.
- What for? - Hurry.
- Come on, hurry up. - All right, hold on.
He's dead meat.
Hey, what are you going to do?
Exterminating the vermin.
- Hello. - Don't you have anything to do?
And what is it you think I'm doing?
You're going around seducing innocent women and swindling them.
You lousy gigolo.
Who are you?
Who am I? What are you going to do about it?
Are you going to come seduce me too?
From your voice, you sound like a kid.
I don't do kids.
- Call me when you're older. - Wow, what a lowlife...
Does your mom know you live like this?
That her son seduces women her age...
And lives like a parasite? Does she know?
I don't have a mom.
Then does your dad know?
Why? You don't have a dad either?
What are you, an alien that fell from outer space?
I found out everything about you.
If you don't stop what you're doing right now,
I'll go to your family. So you'd better watch out.
That their child is destroying another family...
And living lavishly off the money.
I'll go to your family and expose everything.
By any chance, am I dating your mother?
Are you perhaps Min Ju?
- And your mother is Choi Hye Sook? - Why?
Hello?
Hey.
Hey, you lousy gigolo.
Hey, why did you hang up?
You must be bored with your normal life.
How about a taste of prison life for a change?
Just name the date. Since you're going anyway,
I think the sweltering summer heat would be perfect.
What do you think?
If you're done acting up, let's leave it at that.
I was just going to take a little money and leave,
But if you keep provoking me...
I might just become your new dad.
Is that what you want? If you do, just say the word.
You think I can't grant a wish for my daughter?
As your new dad.
What, you bastard?
You're going to pay for this.
I'm already paying for it,
So my little daughter doesn't need to worry about me.
Well, your new dad is very busy, so I have to go.
This bastard is a complete scumbag.
Why? What is he saying?
The person you are calling has their phone turned off.
You will be connected to voicemail.
He turned it off? Unbelievable.
How am I supposed to take this guy down?
Gosh.
(Young Gyu)
Honey, you have a call.
Could you get that for me? I'll be right there.
Yes.
Oh no, they're going to hang up.
Yes, hello.
Isn't this Chairman Jang Hoon Tae's phone?
Yes, it is.
The Chairman can't come...
- to the phone right now. - Let me.
Wait, one moment, please.
Who is it?
Yes, this is Jang Hoon Tae.
This is Han Gyu Young.
You must have left work early.
Yes. I finished up early today. Yes.
If you have a moment, could we meet briefly?
Right now?
Yes, right now.
Is it urgent?
I'll tell you when we meet.
Okay, let's meet then.
Where?
Yes, I know the place.
Okay, then...
I'll head over there in 30 minutes.
Okay.
What could be so urgent that they want to see someone...
Who's already home from work?
I know. She said she'll tell me when we meet. Yes.
Will you be having dinner there?
No, no. Since I can already smell the pollack stew,
I'll meet them quickly and come back to have dinner with you.
Should I get your clothes for you?
Oh, I can get them myself. Go on with your work. Okay?
What is this?
It's the money you lent me, Chairman.
Thanks to your help, I was able to graduate...
And study abroad.
There, I was lucky enough to meet a wonderful man,
And now we're getting married.
Is that so?
That's wonderful. I'll happily accept this.
And congratulations on your marriage.
But...
Shouldn't you tell your mother the news about your wedding?
No.
I told my fiance's family that my mother passed away.
My family, too,
Has been living as if our mother's been dead...
For a long time.
And it's better for your family that way, isn't it, Chairman?
Instead...
Instead of my mother,
Chairman, could you help me once...
No, could you help me twice?
Excuse me?
At the formal family meeting and the wedding ceremony,
You just have to pretend to be my father twice.
Did your father pass away?
As far as I know, he's still alive, isn't he?
He's alive.
Then?
He's alive, but I'm embarrassed...
I mean, I feel hesitant to introduce him to others.
But still, you can't do that.
My future in-laws...
Are extremely prominent people, and my family is not on their level.
I want to be their daughter-in-law so badly,
And I didn't want to feel small, so I lied.
I said my mother had passed away...
And that my father is an entrepreneur.
I even considered hiring an actor...
But you're not a complete stranger,
So I figured it would be better to ask you for help.
It's absurd, isn't it?
I'm sure you're thinking, "Is this girl crazy?"
I know you must be shocked.
But once you see my father,
You'll understand why I'm acting like this.
Please help me, Chairman.
Hey, come on.
What kind of man do you take me, Han Seok Joong, for?
Do I look like I'd take your money and run off somewhere?
Come on. I'm hurt.
Yes?
You're asking why I have a Gyeongsang accent?
Didn't I tell you before?
You and I are from the same hometown.
That's right.
In your hometown, Tongyeong, if you go straight down,
You'll find an island called Bijindo.
What?
It's not Tongyeong, it's Suncheon? Oh my goodness, what have I done?
Sir, what did I just say?
Did I just say Tongyeong?
Oh my goodness, I must be going crazy.
I could just bite my tongue and die. This is unbelievable.
Right, sir.
I'm a real Suncheon man...
And I nearly failed to recognise...
Someone from my own hometown.
Look, sir,
Don't be like that. Please...
Show some Suncheon spirit...
And help me out just this once.
Look, I promise I won't run off with your money.
Okay, sir? Please, just cut me some slack.
Hello?
Hello? Sir. No, sir...
Sir! Hello?
He hung up. My gosh.
Gyu Oh.
I told you to meet me at the pub.
So why did you ask me to come to the rooftop?
What if the family finds out?
This really is the last time.
All right.
You should've just gotten large bills.
Why did you get so many?
It's just bulky.
Cleaning up after your messes...
This is the last time I'm doing it for you...
Instead of Gyu Rim.
I said I get it.
Seriously, next time,
I don't care if you go to jail or die.
You can clean up your own mess.
Are you threatening your own father?
Especially if you bother Gyu Rim,
I swear, Dad, I won't let it slide.
You won't let it slide? So what?
Are you going to hit me?
What number was I on? I completely lost count.
One thousand...
- Hey, hey, give me the money. - Gyu Seo and Gyu Min...
- You shook them down for allowance. - Hey, that's absurd.
I just said my one wish...
Was to eat premium beef until I burst,
And Gyu Min gave me a few bucks to at least buy some imported beef.
That bastard Gyu Seo didn't give me a dime.
Now give me the money, you punk.
Fine, then promise me you won't bother...
Gyu Rim, Gyu Min, or Gyu Seo.
Promise you won't be a nuisance to them anymore.
All right. I said I get it.
So just give me the money, you punk.
Taking back what you gave is the lowest of the low.
Did you leave your money with him?
I'm asking, did you leave your money with him?
When are you going to grow up, Dad? Seriously.
I'll grow up before you do. What?
You punk.
You won't even buy your own dad a roll of gimbap,
So where do you get off yelling at me like that?
Am I a pushover?
Quick, the money. Give me the money.
Don't take that money.
Do you have any idea what he did to earn it?
How do you think he earned that money?
Don't take that money. Please.
What Gyu Seo said...
What does he mean?
Did you...
Did you rob someone for this money?
Are you not going to take it?
I'm asking what you did to get this money.
You're asking how I earned it?
What does it matter how I earned it?
If I earned it through dirty means, you don't need this money?
You're not going to use it?
You wouldn't have robbed someone, surely.
My Gyu Oh is so upright...
And righteous.
When you were little, do you remember your dream was...
To be a police officer catching bad guys?
As long as you didn't steal it, it's fine.
When it comes to money,
You earn it like a dog and spend it like a king.
I'll just count it later.
I'm leaving.
I don't know how much you know, but stay out of it.
How can I stay out of it?
When you're out there doing something so crazy,
How can I possibly stay out of it?
Dad is hopeless,
But you're the bigger problem.
You get it?
What's this?
It's the money I saved from my part-time job.
Why are you giving this to me?
I might be signing with a major company soon.
No, I'm going to.
So quit that crazy stuff you're doing...
Before Gyu Rim finds out.
If Gyu Rim finds out you're living like this,
It'll kill her.
Hey.
Don't get smart.
Forget about part-time jobs and just study.
You're a student, aren't you?
I'll give you one month.
If you don't stop by then,
I'm telling the whole family everything.
It's my life.
I live my own life, and I'll take responsibility for it.
I earn my own money.
So shut your mouth...
And worry about your own life, you punk.
How can you say that?
If I were acting like trash, just like you,
You're saying you'd just stand by and tell me to mind my own business?
Could you really do that?
Yes. I could do that.
I absolutely could.
Stop lying.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm warning you one last time.
Stay out of my life.
If you run your mouth, I'll kill you.
Got it, you little punk?
Running away again?
If you are going to run, do it right this time.
So we never have to see each other again.
Oh my goodness. What's going on?
Goodness, the whole place is going to burn down.
Oh, my goodness. Oh, dear.
How did this happen?
My goodness, did you fall asleep on your feet?
Good grief.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
We should open a window, okay? Oh, dear.
What is it, really?
This is the first time I've ever seen you cry.
I'm not crying.
It's just that these onions are really strong, ma'am.
It's not like this is the first time you've cut an onion.
They're onions. They're supposed to be strong.
- If not strong, are they onions? - But these are extra strong.
We should change our supplier, ma'am.
Yes, okay.
We'll change it right away. Right away.
I'll call Mr. Yang right now, okay?
Did you drink all this?
Why aren't you at work?
I wasn't there. How could you not be there either?
After you left like that, how could I possibly focus on work?
Have you eaten?
I was going to make a feast.
But I burned it all.
Oh, this...
So you drank all this on an empty stomach?
Looks like it.
But I'm not drunk at all.
Right.
It would be weirder if you were okay.
Want a drink?
No, I'm good. For the life of me...
I just can't seem to understand.
What now?
The Gyu Rim I know is not the type of woman to cheat, ever.
That's the Gyu Rim you know too, right?
Let's stop talking about Gyu Rim.
That monkey-faced guy...
I'm sure she only met him after you broke up.
I said, let's drop it.
But the kid is eight years old.
Does that make sense?
You've been thinking it doesn't add up either.
So?
Gyu Rim's son.
I don't think he's that monkey's son.
They don't look anything alike.
If anything, his eyes and nose look more like...
This is too much.
Okay, stop getting carried away, Park Jung Woo.
Gosh.
Hey, wait a minute.
Sorry.
I thought you were someone I knew.
Dad.
You've got it bad. Really bad.
What do you mean?
Yesterday, you chased after a kid about that age.
You even said the same thing.
"Sorry, I thought you were someone I knew."
Who is this person you know?
Who are you looking for so desperately?
Why?
Can't you get Han Gyu Rim's son out of your head?
Your game account has been activated.
What's with him all of a sudden? He's making me nervous.
Let's go to the department store to buy some clothes.
Clothes? Why all of a sudden?
For the formal family meeting.
Who's having a family meeting?
Gyu Young.
What?
I heard her on the phone with her friend just now.
It's at one o'clock today at Changdeokgung in Gangnam.
That's the place famous for marinated short ribs, right?
Are you having a family meeting today?
How did you know?
You're having a family meeting, was I not supposed to know about it?
So annoying.
I wasn't going to invite you, so just pretend you don't know.
How can I pretend I don't know?
- Are you an orphan? - Yes, I told them I'm an orphan,
So just mind your business and drop it.
How can you be an orphan?
You have a father, a sister, and younger siblings.
You have so much family. Hey, that's fraud.
Han Gyu Young.
So you were going to go there all by yourself?
Exactly.
I told them my mom passed away long ago...
And that my father died a few years ago.
I said my siblings were all busy or away on business trips.
You told them that I died?
But I'm standing right here, perfectly fine.
This isn't right, Han Gyu Young.
No matter how crazy you are, you shouldn't have done this.
If I bring you and Father and you end up ruining my marriage,
Are you going to take responsibility?
Why would Father and I ruin your marriage?
Because to me, our family is an embarrassment,
A disgrace, and a humiliation.
My gosh...
What in the world is she saying to us?
Honestly, is there a single decent person in this family?
Other than me, is there anyone you can be proud of?
You're all uneducated, pathetic, and ignorant.
I'll go to a department store and buy the most expensive outfit.
I'll barely say a word so I don't look ignorant.
It's not like you can hide this forever.
Lying like this is wrong.
That's right. If I get all dressed up,
People mistake me for a CEO of a major corporation.
I already told them. I already told them you're dead.
How many times is she going to kill me off today?
Gosh. What do you mean?
What do you mean, where are you going...
That you can't decide whether to go or not?
Well, if you tell me to go, I'll go.
And if you tell me not to go, I won't.
So where is it you're going?
Well, someone asked me a favour, and...
They asked me to attend the family meeting as their father.
Does this person not have parents?
I'm not so sure about that.
Who asked you?
A distant relative. Yes.
Is it someone I know?
Well, you might know them. Yes.
Well...
Have I met them before?
You've probably met them. Yes.
Anyway, should I go or not?
You say they're a relative,
But you don't even know if they have parents.
What's with that?
What's their name?
Their name?
Well...
- Oh my. - It's...
You don't know their name? And they're a relative?
For someone whose name you don't even know,
You're going to attend a family meeting in their place?
Does that make any sense?
Right. It doesn't make sense.
Then should I not go?
Good grief.
A young person like you should be more careful.
(Seonghan High School)
Is this it?
- Yes. - Hey.
You're ashamed of me too, aren't you?
Even though you're so ashamed of me, I was the only one home,
So you asked me to come, right?
- What are you talking about? - Hey.
Am I a disgrace, an embarrassment,
And the lowest of the low to you too?
Did Han Gyu Seo tell you that?
Gyu Seo feels that way too?
That little brat.
Was it Gyu Oh?
Gyu Oh feels that way too?
That kid. And to think he's my eldest son.
Oh, was it Han Gyu Young?
Yes.
That girl has her family meeting today,
And she told her future in-laws...
She said I was dead.
I was completely humiliated by your sister.
What are you talking about?
She said our whole family is an embarrassment.
Everyone and even Gyu Rim... That brat told us not to come.
Fine, I'm not going.
It's so humiliating, I'm not going either.
- Go on in. - Right.
You should at least say goodbye.
(Seonghan High School)
Unbelievable.
It's fine. Don't worry about it. Okay?
She's a girl who thinks she's all that anyway.
She'll handle it herself.
Seriously. That brat.
Hello. Gyu Min, why are you calling at this hour?
Dad took a taxi to go where Han Gyu Young is.
What are you talking about?
I told him to go and crash the whole thing.
What do you mean by that?
Is Han Gyu Young having her family meeting today?
What? Father went to Gyu Young's family meeting?
(Father)
Father, please.
- Gyu Young, you're here? - Yes.
Mother, Father, you're here?
- Did you have trouble getting here? - You're already here, honey?
Is your father here as well?
No. He said he might be a little late for a meeting.
He asked me to tell you he's sorry.
He should be arriving any minute now.
We just came a bit early.
Tell him not to worry and to take his time.
Yes, Mother.
Show my father and mother inside first.
I'll go in with my dad when he gets here.
All right. Please, go on in.
Son, your father and I will head inside first.
You should greet your father-in-law and come in together.
No, it's all right. I can show him in.
It's fine.
- Do as she says. - Yes.
You should go in too.
No, it's okay.
This is my first time formally greeting him,
So of course I should wait and escort him inside.
Honey.
Well,
- I wonder when he'll arrive. - Soon, I guess.
(Father)
Dad.
I'm not too late, am I?
No. You're not late at all.
It's a pleasure to meet you, sir. I'm Kang Sung Wook.
Yes, it's a pleasure to meet you.
Mother and Father are already here.
Let's hurry inside, Dad.
All right. Let's go in.
Where are you, Father?
I don't know either.
Father.
- Where are we? - Ma'am, what neighbourhood is this?
Yaksu-dong.
She said it's Yaksu-dong.
Why are you there?
Weren't you on your way to Gyu Young's?
I got out of the taxi on the way.
I was afraid if I went,
That girl would lose her mind and start foaming at the mouth.
Oh, gosh.
Even though she's my daughter, I'm that scared of Gyu Young.
Ma'am, one bowl of rice, please.
Okay.
You did the right thing.
It was good you got out.
It's a pleasure to meet you all.
This wine might be expensive,
But it's a bit lacking in flavour, don't you think?
This is our first time meeting as in-laws,
And I told you to get the Romanée-Conti.
Well, I actually drink makgeolli or soju more often.
I don't really know much about wine.
Besides, if I drink something this expensive,
I feel like I can't even get properly drunk.
That's right.
Your father is so down-to-earth.
Especially since he looks like a French nobleman.
How many guests are you considering?
Well, we have a small family.
What do you think?
I'd like to have a small wedding.
Thirty people at most?
Oh my, that few?
We were thinking at least 150.
Just invite a similar number to Gyu Young's side.
Son, how can we do that?
Then who do we invite and who do we leave out?
As you may know,
In our world, you have to worry about...
Politics, business, and all sorts of things.
It's a headache.
The bigger the figure,
The more they sulk over trivial matters.
What are your thoughts?
Well, I'd like to do whatever the children want.
It's their wedding, after all.
Yes.
Let's get along well from now on.
- Yes. - Any difficulties, let us know.
- Please take care of our Gyu Young. - Of course.
Oh, right.
I almost forgot this.
- What is this? - The list of wedding gifts.
I put together a simple list.
If your mother were here,
She would have known to prepare everything,
But I was worried you might panic and not know what to do on your own.
Yes, thank you, Mother.
We'll invite you to our home next time.
Yes, thank you.
- Okay. - We'll be on our way, then.
Okay, see you later.
- I'm off. - Goodbye.
I'll call you when I get home.
- Okay. - Sir, I'll be going now.
- All right, see you again soon. - Yes.
(List Of Wedding Gifts And Furnishings)
So, did everything go well?
Thank you so much for today.
I was so nervous you wouldn't come.
But is this a marriage you must have,
Even if it means going to these lengths?
Right.
I may have become an unwilling accomplice,
But this will only hurt your family. And if your in-laws find out later,
It could become a huge problem.
Can you take responsibility for that?
I'll cross that bridge when I get to it.
I don't expect someone like you to understand, Chairman,
But this marriage is something I desperately need.
So much so that I'm willing to do anything.
I see.
I should get going.
My mom really made the right choice to get a divorce.
It's how she got to meet a great man like you.
I really mean it.
What is it? Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
By the way, where's Gyeol?
I've been looking for him, but I can't find him.
He's not in his room?
What?
- Hey, Mom. - Where are you right now?
In front of the burger place.
I'm here to meet someone.
Who?
Game Man.
Why are you meeting him?
He bought me some in-game items.
The most popular and expensive ones, too.
The exact ones I wanted most.
I think he's a nicer person than I thought.
Gyeol, not you too. What are you doing?
You should tell me when things like that happen.
If you haven't met him yet, come home right now.
I already met him.
I'll be home soon. Don't worry.
Hey.
Hello.
I wanted to properly apologise.
I'm the one who should be apologising.
For being disrespectful to an adult. I'm sorry, sir.
Have you eaten dinner?
No.
How about a burger?
Yes, it's my absolute favourite food.
I think I'll have...
The chicken mozzarella.
What? That's my favourite too.
Toppings?
No onions or pickles. Add a fried egg.
Wow, that's my order exactly.
- Should we go in? - Yes.
The person you are calling is unavailable...
(Mom)
Answer it.
It's okay.
Who is it? Your mom?
Mom.
I told you I'd be home soon.
- Let's go. - I haven't finished my burger yet.
Eat at home. Let's go now.
Wait, I forgot my phone.
Got it.
Ms. Han.
Can we talk for a minute?
I have nothing to say to you.
Come on, Mom. You should make up with him.
I'm telling you, he seems like a really great guy.
Why? Because he bought you a few silly in-game items?
You were won over that easily?
You're already letting things like that sway you.
I'm disappointed in you, Han Gyeol.
Ms. Han.
After my mom went to the police station,
She was really shaken up.
She said she even burned the kimchi pancakes.
Let's go.
Gyeol, you go on home.
I'm going to talk to him for a minute.
Are you going to make up?
Good idea. Just go ahead and make up, Mom.
- Go. - Okay, you can do it.
From now on,
Do not arrange to meet with Gyeol.
Do not send him notes...
And do not send him things like game items.
I'm asking you.
I hope we don't have to see each other again.
I have a question.
Is it possible...
He's my son?
Is Gyeol...
My son?
(Love on the Menu)
Gyeol said he's eight years old.
We broke up eight years ago.
Were you cheating on me when we were together?
- That's a lie. - Mom. Ms. Han Gyu Rim.
- Oh, Gyeol. - Why is my mom acting so strange?
She's been acting really strange since she met Game Man.
A negative plus a negative makes a strong positive, you know?
That means a strong positive. A really strong one at that.
- You know me, right? - No, I don't think so.
Snap out of it. I'm not your boyfriend.
I see...
Don't you think this is a bit much?
Then are you going to pay for the apartment, Gyu Young?
Han Gyu Oh, do you have some money?
If you said you were struggling or needed something,
There were plenty of women who would bring it right to you.
It was Gyu Young's formal family meeting.
Gyu Young, it's Mom.
It's been a while, Mom.